# **Terry Ray**

# Full Stack Developer

bignova0117@gmail.com



Victoria, TX, United States

#### SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with 6 years of experience who is early adaptive and follows a trend always. My experience as a web developer at several companies gave me a strong knowledge of traditional web technologies and new coming latest technologies. I amlooking to joinforces to continue to growmyskill set while contributing to the positive outcome of making people richer, smarter, happier.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Full Stack Developer

Factom 06/2022 - 02/2023 USA

- Created an application interface that integrated 35 third-party APIs and improved sales results by 80% within 3 weeks on the job.
- Wrote 200= unit tests to verify the functionality of user interfaces, back-end processing, connectivity, and relational database interactions.
- Implemented software design patterns and best practices, resulting in a 25% reduction in software issues.
- Revamped website flows and navigation menus, reducing the frequency of misdirected customer service queries by 30% and increasing traffic to previously neglected pages.

## Co-founder & Software Engineer

Masma 12/2020 - 06/2022 Japan

- Spearheaded the design and development of the NFT deployer, resulting in a 40% increase in efficiency in deploying non-fungible tokens on various blockchain platforms.
- Successfully implemented over 20 smart contracts and decentralized applications, resulting in a 60% reduction in transaction processing time and a 75% reduction in gas fees.
- Utilized coding, cryptography, and security skills to ensure the secure and seamless operation of the NFT Deployer, resulting in a 90% decrease in the number of security incidents reported by users.

## Full Stack Developer

HBLAB JSC 07/2019 - 12/2020 Japan

- Improved performance by resolving more than 80 critical bugs in the company's products.
- Reduced development time by 70% through code reuse in jQuery libraries for various projects with over 1.8K combined page visits.
- Increased daily traffic from 35% to 80% by repairing existing websites to improve user experience and incorporated SEO.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science

Arizona State University

04/2016 - 03/2018 Lake Havasu, Arizona, US

United States University of California

04/2013 - 03/2016 Berkeley, California, US

#### **SKILLS**

React.js	Next.js	Node.js	Express.js	
MongoDB	MERN	stack	Vue	e.js
Python	Django	Solidity	Web3	
MySQL	Laravel	JavaScript		CSS
PHP H	TML C	/C#		

#### LANGUAGES

LANGUAGES		
English	Proficient	00000
Japanese	Advanced	00000

#### **PROJECTS**

## Mexico Fitvibes Gym Site

https://fitvibesgym.com/

## Telegram Mike Token Mini App

https://t.me/monster\_mysterybot

## American animal doctor's site

https://www.americananimaldoctor.com

#### **MERN Hubbers**

http://hubbers.io

# WhatsApp AI chatbot

+44(772)7617883,TestUI-https://34.244.97.107:3000/

## Music Studio Booking services

https://session-eight.vercel.app/

## Al Airbnbchatbot

https://chatterbnb.com/